let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 31,
    "question": "Which of these is a preventive check according to Malthus?",
    "answer": "foresight",
    "options": [
      "foresight",
      "vice",
      "misery",
      "flood"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 32,
    "question": "Which of these is not a pillar of sustainability?",
    "answer": "trans-boundary sustainability",
    "options": [
      "environmental sustainability",
      "economic sustainability",
      "trans-boundary sustainability",
      "social sustainability"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 33,
    "question": "____ is to identify which potential impacts are relevant to assess (fill in the blank)",
    "answer": "scoping",
    "options": [
      "screening",
      "scoping",
      "reporting",
      "review"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 34,
    "question": "Which of these is a positive check according to Malthus?",
    "answer": "war",
    "options": [
      "late marriage",
      "war",
      "celibacy",
      "moral restraint"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 35,
    "question": "Which of these is a pillar of sustainability?",
    "answer": "social sustainability",
    "options": [
      "social sustainability",
      "industrial sustainability",
      "agricultural sustainability",
      "trans-boundary sustainability"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 36,
    "question": "The demographic transition sees a society move from",
    "answer": "high birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
    "options": [
      "high birth rate, low birth rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
      "low birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
      "high birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
      "high birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, high death rate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 37,
    "question": "The book \"An Essay on the Principle of Population\" was written by",
    "answer": "Malthus",
    "options": [
      "Darwin",
      "Malthus",
      "Spencer",
      "Owens"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 38,
    "question": "The quantum of human impacts is given by",
    "answer": "I = P X A X T",
    "options": [
      "I = P + A + T",
      "I = P + A - T",
      "I = P - (A + T)",
      "I = P X A X T"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 39,
    "question": "____ determines which projects or development require a full or partial impact assessment study (fill in the blank)",
    "answer": "screening",
    "options": [
      "screening",
      "scoping",
      "reporting",
      "review"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 40,
    "question": "According to the Malthusian model",
    "answer": "population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression",
    "options": [
      "population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in geometric progression",
      "population grows in arithmetic progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression",
      "population grows in arithmetic progression, food supply increases in geometric progression",
      "population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression"
    ]
  }
]